Finding Aid for the Ralph Edwards Productions Production Records PASC.0336
UCLA Library Special Collections
- This is Your Life, 1952-1987; Series 1.
  - Research Material, Scripts and Sound Recordings, Subseries 1.
    - Jonathan Winters, 1971 January 18; script (Box 63)
      Subject is a television star and comedian. Includes participants: Ernie Glucksman, producer of the NBC Comedy Hour; Stanley Kramer, producer and director.
    - Colonel A.D. Wintle, M.C., 1959 January 19; script (Box 223)
    - Norman Wisdom, 1957 December 2; script (Box 223)
    - Dean Clarence Wolfe, 1960 August 21; script (Box 225)
    - Isabella Charlotte Woodford, 1961 December 18; script (Box 225)
    - Sergeant James Edward Wood, 1958 October 5; script (Box 225)
    - Marvyn Wood, 1977 July 3; script (Box 221)
    - Gladys Workman, 1957 January 9; script (Box 63)
      Hard luck story. Guests include: Aurelio Arias, friend from her youth in Los Angeles; Hattie M. Brown, mother, from trailer home in South Los Angeles; Ida Ewing, friend from days in Los Angeles after they moved there from San Francisco (late 1930's to early 1940's); Hazel (Mrs. Sydney) Springman, lifelong friend, lived next door when subject's family moved to L.A. in 1909.
    - Eric Worrell, 1976 June 11; script (Box 221)
    - Ed Wynn, 1953 June 3; script (Box 63)
      Subject is a film/radio/television star. Guests include: Gilda Gray, singer, actress, dancer who introduced "The Shimmy" in Ziegfeld Follies; Charles Ruggles, actor; Keenan Wynn, son, actor.
    - Ed Wynn, 1953 June 3 (Box 233)
      Annotated script. Subject is a film/radio/television star.
    - Convict "Johnny X", 1950 January 11; streaming audio (Box 57)
      Radio broadcast. Ex-Convict - Broadcast from Illinois State Penetentiary, Joliet, IL.
    - Convict "Johnny X", 1950 January 11 (Box 233)
      Annotated script. Ex-Convict - Broadcast from Illinois State Penetentiary, Joliet, IL.
    - Charles E. Yeager, 1983 September 10; script (Box 63)
      Subject is Brig. General Charles "Chuck" Yeager Air Force test pilot. Guests include: Gerald Ford, President of the United States.
    - William H. Young, 1959 May 27; script (Box 63)
      Subject is a private detective.
    - Louis Silvie Zamperini, 1954 April 7; script (Box 63)
      Subject is former Olympic Track Star & World War II prisoner of war turned minister. Guests include: Dean Cromwell, track and field coach at the University of Southern California; Jesse Owens, Olympic great; teammate in 1936 Olympics.
    - Louis Silvie Zamperini, 1954 April 7 (Box 233)
      Annotated script. Subject is former Olympic Track Star & World War II prisoner of war turned minister.
    - James Zarb, 1961 February 22; script (Box 225)
    - Bob Zimmer, 1975 August 29; script (Box 221)
  - Publicity, Subseries 2.
    - Alice Lloyd College Newsletter, 1987 (Box 306, Folder 5)
    - Emmy Award Booklet, 1954 (Box 306, Folder 5)
    - Hollywood Reporter Emmy Award Advertisement, 1984 (Box 227)
    - Press Releases (Box 51)
    - Publicity File, 1983 (Box 235)
    - Publicity Flyers (Box 306, Folder 6)
      For the new show, This is Your Life.
    - Publicity for Show on Cover of TV Review Magazine (Box 306, Folder 7)
    - Publicity Reports, 1 folder (Box 231)
    - This is Your Life, Santa Claus!, 1989; sheet music (Box 227)
    - TV Guide Articles, RCA Victor Radio News Article, 1953-1955 (Box 306, Folder 4)
      4 issues. Also includes a People Magazine Game card.
  - Clippings, Subseries 3.
    - Advertising Clippings, 1 folder (Box 234)
    - Article on English Series Host, Michael Aspel, 1988 (Box 302)
    - Article on This is Your Life, 1943 December (Box 306, Folder 2)
      Los Angeles Examiner
    - Assorted Clippings, 1983; 1 folder (Box 235)
    - Assorted Clippings (Box 292)
    - Assorted Clippings (Box 296, Folder 4)
    - Assorted Clippings, 1972 (Box 302)
    - Assorted Clippings, 1 folder (Box 306, Folder 5)
    - Eamon Andrews Memorial, 1987 December 7 (Box 302)
    - English Series Clippings (Box 304)
    - George Romney Clippings (Box 235)
    - Lowell Thomas Clippings, 1 foflder (Box 231)
    - Press Clippings (Assorted) (Box 34)
    - Press Clippings (Assorted) (Box 35)
    - Press Clippings (Assorted), 1967 (Box 232)
    - Press Clippings (Assorted), 1967 (Box 232)
    - Press Clippings (Assorted), 1963 (Box 232)
    - Press Clippings (Assorted), 1993 (Box 235)
    - Press Clippings (Assorted) (Box 295, Folder 3)
    - Ralph Edwards, Family Closets are His Business, 1954 January (Box 306, Folder 2)
      Cosmopolitan magazine article.
    - The Saga of an Honest Con Man, 1953 May (Box 306, Folder 2)
      Published in Tele-Views.
    - This is His Life (Box 306, Folder 2)
      TV Radio Life cover article on Ralph Edwards.
    - This is His Life, 1953 April (Box 306, Folder 2)
      Radio-TV Mirror article on Ralph Edwards.
    - Unidentified Clippings (Box 235)
  - Photographs and Negatives, Subseries 4.
    - Assorted Negatives, negatives (Box 317)
    - Assorted Negatives, negatives (Box 319)
    - English Production Photographs, 1963-1964 (Box 304)
    - English Production Photographs, 1963-1964 (Box 304, Folder 1)
    - Ronal Reagan Host Photographs (Box 295)
      Also includes contracts.
    - Staff and Public Relations Pictures, negatives (Box 313)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Abeles-Anderson), negatives (Box 71)
    - Photographs of Show Subjects (Adkins-Healy), 8 x 10 b & w (Box 226)
      Autographed photographs of program subjects with Ralph Edwards.
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Anthony-Baker, B.), negatives (Box 73)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Baker, D.- Blackstone), negatives (Box 75)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Begay - Klenhard), 1948-1950; negatives (Box 320)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Blair - Bradley), negatives (Box 72)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Braham - Bunker), negatives (Box 74)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Burns - Caulfield), negatives (Box 76)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Chasen - Conn), negatives (Box 70)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Conner - Davis), negatives (Box 68)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Deauville - Dooley), negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Doss -Emerson), negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Falenberg - Foss), negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Foster - Gale), negatives (Box 69)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Garner - Graham, B.), negatives (Box 175)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Graham, V. - Haines), negatives (Box 176)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Hamilton - Herbert), negatives (Box 174)
    - Photographs of Show Subjects (Heckman - Nickermann), 8 x 10 b & w (Box 292)
      Three folders.
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Hersholt - Husing), negatives (Box 177)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Janis - Keaton), negatives (Box 173)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Keil - Lasky), negatives (Box 179)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Laurel & Hardy - Longden), negatives (Box 178)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Louis - MacDonald), negatives (Box 186)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Maclvor - McCoy), negatives (Box 182)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (McCarthy, Charlie - Johnny X), 1948-1950; negatives (Box 318)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (McDougall - Momita), negatives (Box 185)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Moore - Nussbaum), negatives (Box 181)
    - Autographed Photographs of Show Subjects (Norris - Zamperini), 8 x 10 b & w (Box 226)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (O'Brien - Palmer), negatives (Box 184)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Pastor - Presley), negatives (Box 180)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Priest - Rodgers), negatives (Box 183)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Rogers - Ruthling), negatives (Box 163)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Saint - Seligman), negatives (Box 164)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Sennett - Sparksa), negatives (Box 162)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Spirtos - Stuart), negatives (Box 165)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Swanson - Tucker), negatives (Box 166)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Underwood - Warren), negatives (Box 167)
    - Bob Warren, 1954-1957; photographs (Box 231)
      Also includes a Warren biographical note.
      Bob Warren was announcer for the television program for two episodes between 1954 and 1957.
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Watson - Williams, M.), negatives (Box 161)
    - Negatives of Show Subjects (Williams, R. - Zamperini), 1953 June 3-1959 April 8; negatives (Box 209)
  - Production Files, Subseries 5.
    - Assorted Lists and Schedules, 1970-1971 (Box 297, Folder 2)
    - Audition Information (Box 296, Folder 4)
    - Australian Series Subject List, 1975-1976 (Box 304, Folder 3)
    - English Production Information (Box 304, Folder 2)
      Inlcudes: ratings, history notes, list of subjects.
    - English Production Information (Box 304, Folder 2)
      Inlcudes: ratings, history notes, list of subjects, and a photograph of the cast.
    - Fact Cards (Box 296, Folder 4)
      Includes number of shows, number of hosts, etc.
    - New Version Show Description, 1969 March; 2 folders (Box 234)
    - Past Subjects (A-S), 1 folder (Box 234)
      Includes a list of past subjects, and brief descriptions of the shows.
    - Production and Research Protocol, 1 foflder (Box 232)
    - Production Information, 1956-1957 (Box 231)
      Information regarding the shows on the following individuals: Georgia Bowen; Red Nichols; Alexandra Tolstoy; Dean E. Hess; Ernest Borgnine; Darlene Miller; Agnes Underwood; Ernest Breech; Lou Costello; Alice P. Siwundhla; Phil Thatcher; Tennessee E. Ford; Pearl Routan; Thomas Orley; Mike Masaoka; Gladys Workman; Jack Dempsey; Gloria Swanson; Hugh Barr Miller; Constance Hope; Katya Scotnicki; Duke Kahanamoku; Arries Ann Ward; Lawrence Welk; Ivy Baker Priest; George Hayes Gale; Maureen O'Hara; Buster Keaton; Tommy Sands; Ed Bliss; Lila Lee; Minner Pearl; Ted Husing; Ruth Davis; Lee deForest; Thelma White; Rachael Saint; Jesse Laskey; Guy Gabaldon.
    - Production Information, 1958-1959 (Box 231)
      Information regarding the shows on the following individuals: Steve Allen; Roy Campanella; Margaret Abeles; Eddie Albert; Chester Gould; Olga Little; Tim McCoy; Colleen Townsend (Evans); Sadie Glommen; Jim Backus; Samuel G. Fuqua; Lauritz Melchior; Mr. and Mrs. Coy Watson, Sr.; Danny Davey; Marie Wilson; Carlos Romulo; Harry and Allison Neal; Jimmie Rodgers; Robb White; William E. Powers; Desmond Doss; Zaddie Bunker; Ted Lewis; Serge Obolensky; Caleb Chu; Mungai Njoroge; Anny Blyth; Roger Williams; Leo Carrillo; Max Nussbaum; Sidonie Flacco; Holger N. Toftoy; Janet Blair; William H. Young. James obenouf; Frank Capra; Lucille Warnecke; Dick Clark. Also included is information on program sponsorship.
    - Production Information, 1957-1958 (Box 231)
      Information regarding the shows on the following individuals: Phil Harris; Vincent T. Tracy; Gladys Feldman Braham; Frank Lovejoy; Gisele MacKenzie; Jesse L. Lasky; Ronnie Deauville; Billy Graham; Boris Karloff; Marie Killelea; Dennis Weaver; Lela Elliot; Ralph A. Edwards; Sue Sikking; Jimmy Gleason; Ida Lupino; Randall Harris; Frances Farmer; Dennis Branch; Jesse Stuart; Helen Kane; Martha Smith; Belden Paulson; Ben Alexander; Donna Reed; Harry Warren; Felix McCool; Neil Schaffner; Roberta Sherwood; Jessie Steward; Father Bernard Hubbard; Casey Tibbs; Hugh Bentley; Harry Momita; Kirk Douglas; Conrad Hilton; Harvey "Mike" Fetters; Leo Seligmann; James Garner.
    - Production Information, 1955-1956 (Box 231)
      Information regarding the shows on the following individuals: George Burns; Llewellyn J. Scott; Kathleen Norris; John Weber, Jr.; Lt. Col. John P. Stapp; Ilse Intrator Stanley; William Bendix; Julia Judge; Daniele Alberghetti; Ralph Veady; Alice Lloyd; Harold Lloyd; Mary Noyes Dunham; Marion Domenicali; Lew Ayres; H. Clay Conner; Ruth Stromer; Mala Powers; William Hennessey; Bela Herskovits; Virginia Graham Guttenberg; Catherine MacFarland; J. Harrison Heckman; Joe Foss; Marguerita DeSylva; H. Park Tucker; Marian Miller; Robert Cummings; Ruth Joiner; Dore Schary; Marjorie Rambeau; Joseph Anthony; Richard Finnegan; Myrna Loy; James B. Henryx; Ruth Slenczynska; Milton Berle; Alice McDougall; Gilbert Roland.
    - Production Information, 1953-1954 (Box 231)
      Information regarding the shows on the following individuals: Lily Pons; John R. Cates; Mrs. Robert L. Vann; Roy Keyser; Victor McLaglen; Lou Babcock; Eddie Le Baron; Rachel Mellinger; Martha Raye; Eugina Russel; Toots Shor; Edna Gladney; Eddie Cantor; Pansy Stockton; Andrew Murray Griffin; Hope Emerson; Douglas Stringfellow; Danny Thomas; Alice Marble; Ruby Bradley; Gregor Shelkan; Connie Haines; Thelma Morgan; Mack Sennett; Kate Pelham Newcomb; Smith Robinson; Jinx Falkenberg; Louis Zamperini; Hal Foster; Marjorie Williams; Jean Hersholt; George Mardikian; Emma Jo Wengert; Patrick J. Kelly; Alicia Alonzo; Mary Ann; Tom Moore; Frances Nichman; Gilda Grey.
    - Production Information, 1959-1960 (Box 231)
      Includes air dates. Subjects include: Lowell Thomas; Calla E. Varner; Archie Moore; Miroslov Slovak; Charles Ruggles; Count Felix Von Luckner; Tom Dooley; Bill Stern; Bobby Darin; Florence Anderson; Selma Herbert; William Pozonel; Carolyn Jones; Nat King Cole; Martin Palmer; Don McNeill; Karen Rogers; Stephen Boyd; William Kirk; Jonny Londgen; Mervin Leroy; Blackstone; Toni Lee Scott; Carl Reinder; Billy Barty.
      Also included in file is a letter from Ralph Edwards discussing the last program in this series.
    - Production Information, 1960-1961 (Box 231)
      Information regarding the shows on the following individuals: Jackson Wheeler, Jr.; Dave Chasen; Joseph A. Walker; Rafer Johnson; Casey Orr; Lillian Kinkela Keil; Dale Robertson; Hermione Gingold; Dr. Bob Pierce; Debbie Reynolds; Harry Ruby; Mrs. Jonas Veffer; Burch Donahue; Dr. Edmond Souchon; Lenore Conn; Richard Arlen; Peter Palmer; Ole Olsen; Benny Hochman; Robert Horton; Connie Francis; William Frawley; Johnny Grant; Jayne Mansfield; Frank L. Bogart; Norman Alley; Robert Stack; Bernard J. Sheil; William Butler; Clinton H. Goodwin; Cliff Arquette; Joe Louis; Frankie Vaughan; Dr. Richard Ricklefs; Hans Mauch; Maria Vallas Spirtos. Also included is information on program sponsorship.
    - Production Information, 1954-1955 (Box 231)
      Information regarding the shows on the following individuals: Bebe Daniels; Kenneth Porter; Kenyon Scudder; Dorothy Lamour; Roy Davenport; Joe E. Brown; Ruth Lowe; Norman V. Peal; Nellie Logan; Laurel & Hardy; William Wellman; Laurence C. Jones; Clarinda Mason; Jenny Grosinger; Helen Ostrowski; Robert Richards; Eddie Hamilton; Andy Devine; Mae Williams; Sam Magill; Yvonne Kennedy; Clyde Lamb; Carl J. Sedlmeyr; Helen Kellerher; Mickey Walker; Walter Brennan; Wayman Presley; Viola Ruth; Gale Storm; Rene Belbenoit; Kiyoshi Tanimoto; Marjorie Lawrence; Van Heflin; Belle Baker; George Gregory; Frankie Laine; George Bond.
    - Production Information, 1952-1953 (Box 231)
      Information regarding the shows on the following individuals: Laura Stone Marr; Jimmy McHugh; Joan Caulfield; Mary Ross; Casey Stengel; James Templeton; Jeanette MacDonald; Billie Clevenger; James McCain; Mrs. Gus Edwards; Sara Berner; Rock Hudson; Ruth Eiler; Nellie Lutcher; Frank Sparks; Roy Rogers; Harris Pottier; Nadia Scarpitta; Lillian Roth; Allett Radzai; Sheriff Biscauliz; Dinah Shore Montgomery; Frank Coffyn; Lillian Roth; Helene Ruthling; Fifi D'Orsay; Arthur Franz; Virginia Marmaduke; Demetris Apostolan; Eva McGowen; Eddy Janis; Don De Fore; Corny Pierson; Fran Allison; Hannah Block Kohner (Holocaust survivor); Ed Wynn; Pat O'Brien; Vivian Cosby; Mary Healy.
    - Production Information, 1952-1953 (Box 231)
      Information regarding the shows on the following individuals: Laura Stone Marr; Jimmy McHugh; Joan Caulfield; Mary Ross; Casey Stengel; James Templeton; Jeanette MacDonald; Billie Clevenger; James McCain; Mrs. Gus Edwards; Sara Berner; Rock Hudson; Ruth Eiler; Nellie Lutcher; Frank Sparks; Roy Rogers; Harris Pottier; Nadia Scarpitta; Lillian Roth; Allett Radzai; Sheriff Biscauliz; Dinah Shore Montgomery; Frank Coffyn; Lillian Roth; Helene Ruthling; Fifi D'Orsay; Arthur Franz; Virginia Marmaduke; Demetris Apostolan; Eva McGowen; Eddy Janis; Don De Fore; Corny Pierson; Fran Allison; Hannah Block Kohner; Ed Wynn; Pat O'Brien; Vivian Cosby; Mary Healy.
    - Radio Broadcast Principal Subjects List, 1948-1950; 1 folder (Box 234)
    - Ratings History, 1965-1966; 1 folder (Box 234)
    - Reactions of Some Show Subjects (Box 296, Folder 4)
      Includes reactions from: Debbie Reynolds; Ernie Ford;Lowell Thomas; Nat King Cole; Cliff Arquette; Victor McLaglen; Danny Thomas; Harry Blackstone; Hermione Gingold; Martha Ray; Charlie Ruggles; Laurel & Hardy and Phil Harris.
    - Staff Assignments Through the Years (Box 296, Folder 4)
    - Subject Selection, 1968 April 15; 1 folder (Box 234)
      Includes information on how to attract a younger audience.
  - Correspondence, Subseries 6.
    - American League of Professional Baseball Clubs Insurance Issue, 1962 September 9; 5 letters (Box 235)
      Discusses insurance coverage of American League baseball players.
    - Assorted Correspondence (Box 226)
      Includes many "Thank You" letters from show subjects.
    - Assorted Correspondence, 1998; 1 folder (Box 232)
    - Assorted Correspondence, 1967; 1 folder (Box 232)
    - Assorted Correspondence, 1960; 1 folder (Box 232)
    - Assorted Correspondence, 1953-1954; 1 folder (Box 232)
    - Assorted Correspondence, 1959-1961; 1 folder (Box 232)
    - Assorted Correspondence, 1954-1965; 1 folder (Box 235)
    - Assorted Correspondence (Box 291)
    - Assorted Correspondence (Box 296, Folder 4)
    - Assorted Correspondence (Box 301, Folder 1)
      Includes photocopies of letters from: Howard Duff; Betty Lasky; Billy Barty; Virginia Graham; Eddie Cantor, and others.
    - Assorted Correspondence (Box 301, Folder 2)
      From: Billie Burke; Jimmy Mchugh; Billy Graham; Norman Vincent Peale; Myrna Loy.
    - Berle Adams Corrrespondence, 1959-1960; 1 folder (Box 232)
    - Cole, Mrs. Nat (Box 301, Folder 1)
      Thank you letter.
    - Eamon Andrews Correspondence (Box 304, Folder 2)
    - English Production Correspondence, 1979 (Box 304, Folder 1)
    - Fan Mail, 1956 October 15-1957 June 17 (Box 231)
    - Fan Mail, 1958 February 24-1959 January 19 (Box 231)
    - Fan Mail, 1959 January 26-1960 June 13 (Box 231)
    - Fan Mail, 1982; 2 folders (Box 235)
      Regarding the program on Dr. Robert Schuller.
    - Form Letters (Box 231)
    - Frank Land Correspondence, 1 foflder (Box 232)
    - From and To Principal Subjects and Participants, 1970 (Box 301, Folder 4)
    - Holiday Letter to Staff, 1955 January 4 (Box 306, Folder 2)
      Holiday letter from Ralph Edwards on show stationary.
    - Jones, Dr. Laurence, 1954 December 15 (Box 295, Folder 2)
    - Joy Gallagher Correspondence (Box 297, Folder 1)
    - Letters of Permission (Box 301)
      For assorted broadcasts. Includes letters pertaining to: George Burns, Frankie Laine, Robert Young, Gene Krupa, Harry Tobias.
    - Letters of Permission (Box 302)
    - Letters of Permission to Rebroadcast (Box 301, Folder 4)
    - Lewis, Jerry (Box 301, Folder 1)
      To and from Jerry Lewis.
    - Loan of Films, 1954 October 5-1960 February 18 (Box 231)
      Correspondence documenting the request of television footage copies.
    - Lowell Thomas Correspondence (Box 231)
    - Sale of This is Your Life, 1964 April 2; 1 pages (Box 232)
    - Show Subject Suggestions (Box 306, Folder 8)
      Includes: letters of suggestion from Lillian Gish and William F. Buckley, Jr..Also includes letters: suggesting Oskar Schindler as a subject; Los Angeles Dodgers players, Win Clark and Howard Anderson.
    - Show Subject Suggestions; Research Letter for Hedda Hopper Show. (Box 306, Folder 9)
      Includes: letter of suggestion for Chicago White Sox player, Sy Rosenthal; Los Angeles Chargers General Manager, Frank Leahy; golf pro, Ed Furgol. Also included is a letter from Alan Ladd to Hedda Hopper to be used as research for her upcoming appearance on the show.
    - Subject Proposal Correspondence, 1960 April 29 (Box 297, Folder 1)
    - Subject Suggestion Letters (Box 301, Folder 3)
    - Sue Clark Correspondence, 1953; 1 folder (Box 232)
    - Thank You Letters (Box 301, Folder 2)
    - Thank You Letters (Box 301, Folder 3)
    - To Mrs. G.R. Edwards, 1956 July 17 (Box 297, Folder 1)
      Suggestion of Edward MacHugh as show subject.
    - Tucker, Sophie (Box 301, Folder 1)
      Thank you letter from Tucker.
    - Wayman Presley Correspondence (Box 235)
  - Business Papers, Subseries 7.
    - 30th Anniversary Special (Box 235)
      Notes and statistics.
    - Analysis of Subjects (Box 231)
      8 Season analysis of subjects as to categories and age groups.
    - Assorted Papers, 1957-1958 (Box 295, Folder 2)
    - Assorted Papers, 1957-1959 (Box 296, Folder 7)
      Includes: correspondence; show subject lists; station lists; clippings; material pertaining to the Eddie Cantor episode; script for the Audie Murphy episode.
    - Charity Fund Raising (Box 297, Folder 2)
    - Contracts, 1963 May; 1folder (Box 232)
    - Fund Raising (Box 297, Folder 2)
    - Hollywood Museum Donation, 1962-1963; 1 folder (Box 232)
    - How Did "This is Your Life" Originate?, 1978 January 26 (Box 296, Folder 4)
      Four page answer from Ralph Edwards.
    - NBC License Agreement, 1963; 1 folder (Box 232)
    - NBC Politics and Political Figures Memorandum, 1958 (Box 296, Folder 6)
      NBC memo on the NBC procedures to be followed with regard to the appearance of candidates for public office on NBC television network programs.
    - NBC Purchase Agreement Memos, 1963; 1 folder (Box 232)
    - NBC TV Station List, 1955 October 28 (Box 231)
      Includes state and city call letters and broadcast times.
    - NBC TV Station List, 1954 October 14 (Box 231)
    - NBC TV Station List, 1957 March 25 (Box 231)
    - NBC TV Station List, 1953 September (Box 231)
    - Negative License Agreement Memos, 1963; 1 foflder (Box 232)
    - Policy Memos, 1961 April; 1 foflder (Box 232)
    - Rating Reports (Box 231)
    - Ratings, 1956-1959 (Box 296, Folder 6)
    - Ratings Report, 1983-1984; 2 binders (Box 235)
    - Ratings Report, 1987; 1 folder (Box 235)
    - Ratings Report, 1984-1985; 1 binder (Box 235)
    - Ratings Reports, 1956-1960; 1 folder (Box 231)
    - Sales Presentation Information, 1950; 1 folder (Box 234)
    - Sound Recording Information, 1958-1959; 1 foflder (Box 232)
      Includes royalty statements.
    - Statue of Liberty Program Status Report, 1985 February 19 (Box 235)
    - Subject Descriptions (Box 296, Folder 4)
      Brief descriptions of select show subjects.
    - Subject Submissions (Box 297, Folder 3)
  - Ephemera, Subseries 8.
    - Assorted Ephemera (Box 292)
      Includes related comic books, storyboards, show tickets.
    - USS Arizona Memorial Memorial Day Program, 1994 May 30 (Box 306, Folder 2)
      Ralph Edwards raised funds to provide seed money for the USS Arizona memorial on a program featuring the life of Rear Admiral Samuel G. Fuqua, the last man to step off the Arizona.
  - Sound Recordings, Subseries 9.
    This sub-series consists of general sound recordings used for all episodes of the program. For sound recordings of specific episodes, see sub-series 1.
    - CBS Radio Promos, 1950 September 7-1958 June 6; streaming audio
      Announcers: Art Balinger & Ralph Edwards.
      Five promos announcing TIYL Radio moving to CBS Tuesday, May 9 (1950)
    - Theme, streaming audio
- Truth or Consequences, 1940-1988; Series 2.